{
    "subject": "resource/Broadminded_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English",
    "human_readable": "The language of the film 'Broadminded' is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9794617295265198,
            "question": "Is the film 'Broadminded' spoken in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9404622316360474,
            "question": "What language is the film 'Broadminded' in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8048490285873413,
            "question": "Could someone who speaks English understand 'Broadminded'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7980866432189941,
            "question": "Does the film 'Broadminded' feature dialogue primarily in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7525734901428223,
            "question": "Is it possible to understand the film 'Broadminded' without knowing English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7404375672340393,
            "question": "If the film 'Broadminded' was dubbed, what language would likely be used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5191462635993958,
            "question": "What language barrier would viewers encounter if they didn't speak English and watched 'Broadminded' without subtitles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5042836666107178,
            "question": "What language would subtitles be needed for if someone wanted to watch 'Broadminded'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4952544569969177,
            "question": "What is the primary mode of communication in the film 'Broadminded'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4668332040309906,
            "question": "Would someone who doesn't speak English need subtitles to watch 'Broadminded'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the film 'Broadminded' is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_235_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary mode of communication in the film 'Broadminded'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_235_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language would subtitles be needed for if someone wanted to watch 'Broadminded'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_235_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language barrier would viewers encounter if they didn't speak English and watched 'Broadminded' without subtitles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_235_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_235_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n### Explanation:\nThe documents provide information about a film titled \"Broadminded\" (1931) and its release details, including the director Mervyn LeRoy. The query asks whether the language of the film 'Broadminded' is English. Given that it has an English title (\"BROADMINDED\") and was produced by Warner Brothers in 1931 during a period when Hollywood primarily produced films in English, we can infer that the language of the film is indeed English. Therefore, the answer is \"yes.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}